And today's meeting of the Miami Special Utility Authority.
Item two is invitation by the staff member of Mustard Sea Christian Church Kyoto.
Amy Homer said, Amy are you from Miami?
I don't thought I recognized your last name.
Well, if you don't mind doing the education and I understand you have a brief presentation,
you want to give also about good planning.
Okay, come here.
Each person that's here in the day and the years of the world is leaving here from that.
But I believe that you would bust them and get them to a prayer house and get them ready to leave the city.
I don't know what I'm going to do.
Knowledge and send it in this situation.
And while they're also creating a new kids' access to some people around this community, you do.
And I believe that that would change our hearts and that we would be alike.
And all of this is going to be a new issue.
We're going to do a little bit of a mess.
This thing is so much to you, I'd like to press and press.
And then I'll just do a little bit of a thing.
It's going to be a mess today.
And you're going to make it really a bit of a mess.
I'm just going to do a little bit of a thing.
Thank you.
You're all right.
Amy, you have a pretty soft voice.
You have to speak up.
We don't have a big sound.
Because it's a great sound.
If you don't have a mic.
Okay.
Well, I'm glad you're here.
Over there.
And I am going to take the message.
And we can do that.
Sure.
I'm really excited to.
It's a great day.
I'm going to share some things.
I really passionate about something.
The words that is up in my heart.
I'm just, actually.
The message that we're going to work as an organization.
That's it.
Thank you.
Just.
And.
So.
Okay.
It's.
So.
And.
And so.
So.
and when I think about Japan, I think about that.
I think about from instance what Dream is says,
I call him and then move not the week.
And how do we believe in him?
How do we make a record?
How do we hear about someone who teaches him?
How do we teach him a fair set?
And so, most of you have seen network, it's our dream that there would be churches and all throughout
and in that huge person would have a chance to hear the gospel and to respond to that.
So, my team and I are the thing for those churches and individuals that would be interested in partnering with us by nature,
and I am looking to raise $3,8 million in public support and $10,000 in one time support.
So, if there is a monthly interested in partnering with me in this,
I would also like to share more about what's going on in Japan and opportunity that's ahead and good to do this.
Thank you, thank you.
Are you working with the Minister of Alliance?
No, I would just recommend that you migrate you out to that group also for support.
Okay?
All right.
Thank you.
Okay.
Next item is the pledge.
We're going to stand back at that group.
We know if you would do it by the flag?
Yes, sir.
I would like to engage you to the flag of the United States of America and to the very public for which it stands.
One nation.
I would like to thank you for this vote with liberty and justice for all.
Thank you.
Okay.
Item 4 is public input unscheduled personal appearances and when you're on to wishes to address the council on any of the agenda.
There being not on a file's consent agenda staff is recommending item 6 and 7, which are the claims of the minutes for the consent agenda.
If there are no questions on any of those items, if you're going to obtain a motion please.
And a second.
Second.
Local.
Chalice in.
What's the.
Forster.
Lewis.
Cholice.
All right.
I made this a little bit C17.
A.
This is just more of a.
I wanted to order.
This was placed on the MSUA agenda inadvertently.
It should have been on the city council agenda.
But since we've already put it out.
What I've asked Tyler to do is go ahead and make the presentation because it's pretty interesting what we're going to do.
what we're going to do. But the actual bit of work will be on the next city council agenda
on the consent agenda. So on the next, we're going to just ask that it be put off,
but since we're already geared up to give the presentation, we thought we'd give the presentation
tonight.
So if you're going to start a BRC, keep it up for a bit, just look fine. They're fighting
in the EOTX.
to go into the campus, this is the airline through campus.
So, you know, if you know, I came out slip-on and said,
up, going in and excavating the whole side,
and putting you pipe in, they actually put a material
and they're almost like a sock, run it all the way through the pipe,
and then cured it.
And then, instead of talking about control car through there,
with a little cutter on it, it cuts out all the surfaces.
So, you know, going there and just sort of being the soul,
you know, how you excavation side of the campus.
So, it's kind of going to be project to lessen any damage to the soul.
And what's the material that used to it?
So, this is kind of about that.
This one's a belt sock, they have either a fiber or a belt,
a material that we're using as a belt.
And it's infused with a rosin.
Yeah.
And then the rosin, they run ultra-hot water through it.
And that causes a reset, exactly.
This one is slightly different.
Instead of using the steam or the hot water to cure it,
this one's actually going to use UV light.
So, we're not really losing very much diameter this way.
No.
So, we're going to get it smooth.
And you have to wear the streets, you know,
the streets get it to the lines and it removes all the tree roots from roots.
And you wear the pipes as a material to be able to play a pipe.
I mean, it makes it one piece.
So, we received you a bit for this.
I'm a little bit of a 92,000 dollars.
So, it's like being able to bring this back on the contingent of the city side.
And where is this going to start?
And where's it going to end?
It starts on.
I street, they're in front of EEO.
There's a manhole right there.
So, right there, they'll actually insert their song right there.
And they'll go to EEO Street, the street that runs there by the stadium.
So, let's do it on.
I actually run down and do this and have a campus right there.
It's approximately 12,000.
It's a GPP.
OK.
Did you tell them issues being exposed?
It's just getting approved.
Now I don't believe so.
OK.
Any other questions?
I'm interested in technology.
I guess we'll be seeing some of this on some of our other infrastructure down the road.
Yes.
Good.
Awesome.
OK.
Thanks, Tyler.
Thank you.
So, we're not actually, we're not voting on to award the bid.
This is really, definitely.
This is a council item.
And again, we will have it on the consent agenda at our party meeting.
OK.
Any new business?
Staff reports are in your packet.
They're available for questions.
Any community announcements?
Do we have most to adjourn?
Make a motion.
Second.
We'll call.
Four-star.
Aye.
We'll assign.
Western.
Aye.
Johnson.
Show.
Aye.
We will take.